[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":33186,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":210793,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure th at when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":7232,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":218026,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":24767,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":242794,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1617,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":244412,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":3560,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":247972,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1510,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":249482,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the secon d one to  it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3","6","0"],"rt":15592,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":265074,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":823,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":265897,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":2149,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":268047,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":853,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":268901,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":2425,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":271327,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3  +<sub>6 </sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1663,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":272991,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":2999,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":275990,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":891,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":276882,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3?  <br />< br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":2072,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":278954,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":894,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":279848,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get you r result .)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":2357,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":282205,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":900,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":283106,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":1825,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":284931,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":855,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":285787,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7","1"],"rt":6162,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":291950,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1031,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":292982,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":14296,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":307279,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its  own inve rse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":79777,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":387057,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":5074,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":392132,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1485,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":393618,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> ? <br /> <br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":2820,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":396439,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1909,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":398349,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":1802,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":400151,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":969,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":401121,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":3020,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":404141,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity  under + <sub>6</sub>.","rt":1431,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":405572,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":3465,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":409038,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":5416,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":414455,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can  simply  be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":18428,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":432883,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub> 6</sub>  2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":118730,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":551613,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":7264,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":558878,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1078,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":559956,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br / ><br />  (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":2418,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":562374,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":16869,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":579243,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub> 6</sub>?  <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":53381,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":632625,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":3512,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":636137,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":11948,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":648085,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1648,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":649733,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback  to make  sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":15348,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":665081,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":3358,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":668439,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1255,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":669694,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":3057,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":672752,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["11","2"],"rt":5678,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":678431,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":7566,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":685997,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":4327,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":690324,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":2835,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":693160,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":4245,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":697405,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What  is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"four plus one is not nine or greater so we can't divide to get a smaller number so the added result is the answer.","explanation_history":["four plus one is not greater tha","four plus one is not greater th","four plus one is not gre","four plus one is not gr","four plus one is not g","four plus one is not nine or greater so we can't divide to get a smaller number so the added result is the answer."],"response_history":["5"],"rt":49233,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":746638,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"We add up both numbers and divide by nine t o get a  smaller number because the added result is nine or greater. After dividing by nine we get our answer.","explanation_history":["We c","We adde","We add up both numbers and divide by nine to get a smalle rn","We add up both numbers and divide by nine to get a smalle r","We add up both numbers and divide by nine to get a smalle ","We add up both numbers and divide by nine to get a smaller number because the con","We add up both numbers and divide by nine to get a smaller number because the co","We add up both numbers and divide by nine to get a smaller number because the c","We add up both numbers and divide by nine to get a smaller number because the adee","We add up both numbers and divide by nine to get a smaller number because the ade","We add up both numbers and divide by nine to get a smaller number because the added result is re","We add up both numbers and divide by nine to get a smaller number because the added result is r","We add up both numbers and divide by nine to  get a s maller number because the added result is greater","We add up both numbers and divide by nine to get a smaller number because the added result is g","We add up both numbers and divide by nine to get a smaller number because the added result is nine or greater. After dividein","We add up both numbers and divide by nine to get a smaller number because the added result is nine or greater. After dividei","We add up both numbers and divide by nine to get a smaller number because the added result is nine or greater. After divide","We add up both numbers and divide by nine to get a smaller number because the added result is nine or greater. After dividing by nine we get our answer."],"response_history":["3"],"rt":53521,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":800159,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0-8","explain":true,"explanation":"answers can only be from zero to itself subtracted by one.","explanation_history":["anser","anse","answers can only be from zero to itself mises","answers can only be from zero to itself mise","answers can only be from zero to itself mis","answers can only be from zero to itself mines","answers can only be from zero to itself mine","answers can only be from zero to itself minis","answers can only be from zero to itself mini","answers can only be from zero to itself mines one","answers can only be from zero to itself mines on","answers can only be from zero to itself mines o","answers can only be from zero to itself mines ","answers can only be from zero to itself mines","answers can only be from zero to itself mine","answers can only be from zero to itself minees ","answers can only be from zero to itself subrt","answers can only be from zero to itself subr","answers can only be from zero to itself subtracted by  one."],"response_history":["0-8"],"rt":107499,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":907659,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":12892,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":920552,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":2774,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":923327,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":6887,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":930215,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"Find a number that when added up comes to nine.","explanation_history":["Find a number that a","Find a number that when added up comes to i","Find a number that when added up comes to nine."],"response_history":["6"],"rt":35452,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":965667,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"Adding two to itself until it goes over nine then subtracting nine. If we keep going we can tell it goes through add even numbers then all odd numbers.","explanation_history":["Adding two up until it ","Adding two to itself until it goes over nine then substracting nine.","Adding two to itself until it goes over nine then subtracting nine. If we keep going we can tell it goes through add even numbers then all odd numbers."],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":92367,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1058034,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"There can only be multiple of three.","explanation_history":["There can onlyh b","There can onlyh ","There can onlyh","There can only be multiple of three. "],"response_history":["No"],"rt":22702,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1080736,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","explain":true,"explanation":"I went through the multiples of five until I saw a pattern.","explanation_history":["0","5,10","5,1","5,1,6,1","5,1,6,5","5,1,6,2,7,3,0","5,1,6,2,7,3,8,4","I went through the multoi","I went through the multo","I went through the multiple ","I went through the multiples o f","I went through the multiples o ","I went through the multiples of five nu","I went through the multiples of five n","I went through the multiples of five until I saw a per","I went through the multiples of five until I saw a pe","I went through the multiples of five until I saw a pattern."],"response_history":["Yes"],"rt":123353,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1204090,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"I went up the multiples of six until I saw a pattern.","explanation_history":["6,12,18,24,30,36","6,3,18,24,30,36","6,3,0,24,30,36","6,3,0,6,30,36","6,3,0,6,3,36","I went up the mut","I went up the multiples of six until I saw a pe","I went up the multiples of six until I saw a pattern."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":54092,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1258183,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think o f. If yo u need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":15890,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1274073,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"+n = 1+n","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["+n = 1+n"],"rt":31352,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1305425,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"+n = x+n","explain":true,"explanation":"I realize it could be any counting number.","explanation_history":["I realize it  could b e any counting number."],"response_history":["+n = x+n"],"rt":34513,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1339938,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"See if the element x is not a multiple of the +n.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["not us","not u","not sure.","See if only there","See if only ther","See if only the","See if only th","See if only t","See if only ","See if only","See if onl","See if on","See if o","See if the element x is not  a","See if the element x is not  ","See if the element x is not a mul","See if the element x is not a mu","See if the element x is not a m","See if the element x is not a ","See if the elemen t x is n ot an ","See if the element x is not an","See if the element x is not a multiple of the c","See if the element x is not a multiple of the +n."],"rt":188146,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1528084,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":10828,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1538913,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":9754,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1548668,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["True"],"rt":14303,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1562972,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"True","explain":true,"explanation":"If x is a multiple then any multiple of x is not going to have a reminder left over so its not goin g to be  a generator.","explanation_history":["If x is a multiple then any multiple of x is not doesn","If x is a multiple then any multiple of x is not does","If x is a multiple then any multiple of x is not doe","If x is a multiple then any multiple of x is not do","If x is a multiple then any multiple of x is not d","If x is a multiple then any multiple of x is not going to have a reminder left over so its not going to be a generator."],"response_history":["True"],"rt":52160,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1615133,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":82835,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1697969,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Always","explain":true,"explanation":"guess","explanation_history":["T","yes","ye","y","guess"],"response_history":["Sometimes","Always"],"rt":166714,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1864684,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":11164,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1875848,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1649,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1877498,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"25","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["25"],"rt":3042,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1880540,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree ","Maste rs Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Bachelors Degree","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Bachelors Degree"],"rt":3377,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1883917,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"multi-variable calculus, discrete math, linear algebra","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["multivariable calculus, discree","multivariable calculus, discrete math","multi-variable calculus, discrete math, ","multi-variable calculus, discrete math,","multi-variable calculus, discrete math, linear algebra"],"rt":106567,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1990484,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"5 - used it, remember and understand it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"rt":14603,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2005087,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"4 - used it but not often or recently","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4 - used it but not often or recently"],"rt":10109,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2015196,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - not at all","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - not at all"],"rt":11829,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":2027026,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":3951,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":2030978,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"rt":4431,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":2035410,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Male"],"rt":2026,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2037436,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are yo ur nativ e language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"english","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["english"],"rt":4801,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":2042237,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["on","o","no"],"rt":15675,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":2057912,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"none","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["none"],"rt":3537,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":2061450,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]